napower.biz 2012-11-27

# North American Power

We are committed to protecting your privacy at North American Power & Gas LLC. We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that we have not mentioned in this statement. North American Power & Gas LLC will not disclose your personal information without your express consent unless required to do so by law.

##### Collection and Use of Data 

We may ask you for information that personally identifies you, such as your name, phone number, e-mail address, and mailing address. We will only use your personal information within North American Power & Gas LLC. In the future, you may be able to "opt out" of certain uses of your personal information as well as review or request changes of your personal information. We will not share your personal information with anyone else without your permission. We may also track the Internet addresses of our visitors to analyze data for trends and statistics, however, this information will not allow us to identify who you are.

##### Updating and Removal of Data 

You may remove your name from our mailing list at any time by emailing us at [info@napower.com](mailto:info@napower.com) with your request.

##### Security of Personal Information

We have standard industry security mechanisms and procedures to protect data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

##### Third parties

North American Power & Gas LLC. may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of customer visits to our Web site each month but does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member, unless that member has given us permission to share that information. We may also provide log files and other databases of user information to third parties for analysis, so we can get a better understanding of traffic through our site and thus improve our content offerings. North American Power & Gas LLC may use third party companies to provife delivery of e-mail newsletters and other messages over e-mail. North American Power & Gas LLC. uses a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our sites. This company may use information about your visits to our and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, we share web site usage information about visitors to our sites with this company for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements on our sites. Also be aware that we may buy and sell business assets or divisions; customer information is generally part of such a sale.

##### Forward Looking Statements

Certain statements included in press releases on this site are forward-looking and are subject to certain risks and uncertainties. The results or events predicted in these statements may differ materially from actual results or events. Such statements are generally accompanied by words such as "anticipate", "believe", "estimate", "expect", "foresee", "intend", "plan", or similar statements. Factors that may cause results or events to differ from current expectations include, but are not limited to, general economic and business conditions, conditions affecting the industries served by North American Power & Gas LLC, conditions affecting the North American Power & Gas LLC customers, partners and suppliers, the effect of national and international political and economic conditions including currency exchange rate fluctuations, North American Power & Gas LLC's reliance on partners and the ability and willingness of partners to devote their resources to sales of our services, the ability of our sales force to increase sales, competition, including the impact of price competition, the impact of rapid technological and market change, loss of business or credit risk with major customers. Accordingly, North American Power & Gas LLC believes that the expectations reflected in such forward-looking statements are reasonable, there can be no assurance that such expectations will prove to be correct. Any forward-looking statement speaks only as of the date on which such statement was made, and North American Power & Gas LLC undertakes no obligation to update or revise any forward-looking statements, whether as a result of new information, future events or otherwise. No assurance can be given that actual results, performance or achievement expressed in, or implied by, forward-looking statements within this disclosure will occur, or if they do, that any benefits may be derived from them.

##### Obtaining your consent

By using our web site, you give North American Power & Gas LLC permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register at North American Power & Gas LLC, you authorize North American Power & Gas LLC to use information you provide to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. North American Power & Gas LLC may occasionally amend this policy. We suggest that you bookmark this page and check to see if it has changed from time to time. 

##### Questions?

If you wish to change any information you have given us, or have any questions on our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at [info@napower.com](mailto:info@napower.com).
